Guide to the Book and Bond, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Book and Bond, Yale University, records
1899-1954
RU 60
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5.25
(5 boxes)
The records consist of constitution, correspondence, committee reports and minutes, publications, expense sheets, dance and banquet programs, photographs, song lyrics, memorabilia and membership cards related to the founding, governance, and activities of the Book and Bond social fraternity.
Yale University. Book and Bond
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies and organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in two series: I. Administrative Files, 1899-1954. II. Membership Files, 1899-1934 and subsequent accession.
Biographical / Historical
Book and Bond (also known as Phi Kappa Epsilon and Ammanot Club) was established as a social fraternity at Yale University in October 1899. Fraternity rooms included facilities at 823 Chapel Street, Ammanot Hall at the Gamble and Desmond building, and 8 Prospect Place. Book and Bond disbanded in 1935.
Biographical / Historical
The Fraternity of Book and Bond (also known as Phi Kappa Epsilon and Ammanot Club) was established at Yale University in October 1899 by Benjamin F. Nead and E. H. Berner as a social club to "stand for the University's true democratic principles." Responding to Yale's transition from a college to a university in 1887, society members sought to strengthen ties among students in Yale's growing number of schools and departments. Book and Bond adopted a constitution on October 8, 1899 and held informal meetings until March 22, 1900, when members revised the constitution and elected the society's first slate of officers. On May 2, 1900, a committee reported on a meeting at which President Arthur Twining Hadley gave his sanction to the fraternity.
On September 27, 1900, Book and Bond held its first meeting in its fraternity rooms at 823 Chapel Street. Several years later, members voted to rent a room at the Gamble and Desmond building. This room was named Ammanot Hall and served as the location for fraternity functions until 1913, when the society voted to purchase a residence at 8 Prospect Place to serve as a permanent club facility.
Book and Bond's membership consisted of active (undergraduate), graduate (alumni), and honorary members. These individuals kept in touch in publications including an annual bulletin and the newsletter, Spring-It. Members also participated in "round robin" letter campaigns during which correspondence was circulated among members of an initiation group to communicate during the summer and after graduation.
Book and Bond activities included annual banquets, initiation ceremonies, dances, canoe trips, teas, receptions, and amateur theater. The official insignia of the society depicted a book surrounded by a gold, buckled strap engraved with the letters ΦΚΕ that signified "a secret student body, bound together by an unbreakable bond."
During 1923-1925, active members, looking to ensure the financial solvency of the fraternity, proposed that alumni members take out policies from New England Mutual Life Insurance Company with Book and Bond as an absolute beneficiary. This plan was ultimately rejected by the society's Graduate Council.
Book and Bond disbanded in 1935.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of constitution, correspondence, committee reports and minutes, publications, expense sheets, dance and banquet programs, photographs, song lyrics, memorabilia and membership cards related to the founding, governance, and activities of the Book and Bond social fraternity.
College students -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Book and Bond
- Administrative Files, 1899-1954; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of files by format or subject containing correspondence, committee reports and minutes, publications, expense sheets, dance and banquet programs, photographs, song lyrics and other memorabilia related to the founding, governance, and activities of Book and Bond. The records are arranged alphabetically within topical headings. The bulk of the records are related to the activities of various regular and special committees, such as the archival, house, insurance, and membership committees. These committees were charged with tasks ranging in scope from developing a proposal to acquire a club house, to selecting the society's stationary to amending the society's bylaws and constitution. Other records document interactions among the active and graduate membership; the society's relationship with other fraternities and Yale administrators; financial matters; annual social events; and fraternity rituals and traditions.
  - Annual bulletins and Spring-It [alumni newsletters], 1905-1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committees
    - Archival and historical committees
      - Accounts of Book and Bond's founding, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence [mainly from alumni], 1909-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence to alumni requesting information on Book and Bond's history [includes responses], 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Expenses, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Historical Notes [includes brief notes about members and lists of honorary members, graduate council members, and secretaries], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Investigation to locate founding documents, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Military service of members, 1915-1920, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Officers of Book and Bond, 1899-1915 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Petition to the Yale University Council, Praying for the Recognition of the University Society of Book and Bond [includes report of meeting with the University president], 1900 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Reports [weekly], 1904-1931, undated (Box 1, Folder 11 - 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1907-1931, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Executive committee [meeting agendas and reports], 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Honor roll committee [report and vouchers], 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - House committee
      - Ammanot Hall [room rented for fraternity activities], 1906 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Fundraising for house [graduate members' responses], 1909 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Glass plate negative of 8 Prospect Place property, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Proposal to purchase and remodel 8 Prospect Place property [includes illustrations], 1913, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Reports, 1900-1931 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Insurance committee
      - Correspondence with life insurance agents [includes bids], 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Proposed Plans for the Graduate Dues: Chart Prepared by the Insurance Committee, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Reports
        - Comparisons of insurance plans, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Insuring furniture, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Proposal to have alumni members take out policies from New England Mutual Life Insurance Company with Book and Bond as "absolute" beneficiary, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Membership committee
      General
      See also: Series II. Membership Files, 1899-1934
      - Alphabetical List of All Undergraduate Members of Fraternities in the Academic, Law, and Scientific Departments of Yale University, Correct to March 1923, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence [declines for honorary membership; recommendations for potential members], 1901-1922 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - "Hold offs" [new member agreements to refrain from pledging other societies], 1901-1908 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Honorary members, 1911-1920 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Initiation [invitations for membership, ritual procedures, initiation committee reports and notes], 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Reports [annual], 1915-1923 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Reports [weekly], 1902-1925 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Resignation of Member, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Skits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous, 1901-1931 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Rules committee
      - Amendments to bylaws and constitution, 1900-1923, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Bylaws [partial], undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Card files [records of motions made at meetings], 1900-1902 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Order of business at meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Special committees [such as insignia, publications, secret code and grip, and wedding gifts], 1900-1925 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1901-1929 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Bicentennial celebration, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - National fraternities, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Round robin letters [correspondence among active and graduate members]
      - 1913 group, 1911-1916 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - 1918 group, 1912-1930 (Box 1, Folder 45 - 46)
      - 1930 group (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Suggestions to group secretaries to begin round robins, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Yale fraternities and officials [mainly regarding establishment of interfraternity council], 1903-1928 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Events
    - Annual banquet programs, correspondence and budget, 1901-1924 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Dance programs, 1911-1917 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Initiation programs, 1910-1913 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Finances
    - Balance sheets and financial statements, 1928-1930 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Contracts for house repairs and services, 1904-1924 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Monthly report of treasurer, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Graduate Council [correspondence and meeting minutes], 1903-1932 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Songs, 1904, 1924, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous, 1903-1929 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Membership Files, 1899-1934; Series II
  This series contains records related to the members of Book and Bond. The bulk of the series contains individual member files of active (undergraduate), graduate (alumni), and honorary members that are arranged alphabetically. The date of each member file is the year during which an individual became an active, graduate or honorary member of Book and Bond. The membership files include name cards listing biographical information about members' family history, secondary and undergraduate education, and professional accomplishments. Some member files contain additional documents such as war record questionnaires, wedding and birth announcements, correspondence, photographs, and clippings. Other folders in this series include chapter address books, membership lists, and lists of members' marriages and children. Membership committee files are listed in under Series I, Administrative Files.
  - Address books, 1904-1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lists of members, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lists of members' children, 1915-1921 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lists of members' marriages, 1914-1921 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Member files
    - Abbott, Warren Dwight Jr., active 1929 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Aikens, Claude Gitt, active 1912 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Albert, (Charles) Gerald, active 1931 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Albro, Thomas Cranston III, active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Frederick Crosby, active 1916 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Amis, Reese Thomas, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Anderson, Allen Morgan, active 1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Karl Brooke, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Andrews, Clarence Edward, active 1904 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Andrews, Floyd Whipple, active 1904 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Arnold, Edwin Gustaf, active 1924 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Arnstein, William Eugene, active 1928 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Ash, John Frederick Jr., active 1932 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Asherman, Edward Goodwin, active 1932 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Atherton, Harlan Ernest, active 1903 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Athey, Glenn Castle, active 1920 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Ayres, Charles Clark, active 1912 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Baker, Arthur Alan, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Baker, George Merrick, charter member n.d. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Baker, Raymond Frank, active 1910 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Barber, Edward Johnson, active 1903 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Barker, Charles Albro, active 1924 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Barrows, Paul Mather, active 1910 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Bassford, Henry Hall, active 1931 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Bates, Joseph Sumner, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Batty, Norman Coulston, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Bartlett, Burton William, active 1910 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Beadle, Leonard Aiken, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Beardslee, Clark Smith, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Beardslee, Claude Gillette, active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Beardslee, Raymond Augustus, active 1903 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Beardslee, Sidney Alvord, active 1914 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Beardsley, Warwick, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Beeman, Allen Everett, honorary member n.d. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Belden, Arthur Glenney, active 1901 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Bell, Walter Andrew, active 1913 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Benner, Edward Hopkins, active 1899 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Bennett, Irving Theodore, active 1919 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Berkeley, Maurice Fitzhardinge, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Berry, James Brewton, active 1923 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Bilger, Hans L., active 1916 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Bishop, Fred Margeson, active 1913 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Bishop, Wilfred Merriman, active 1916 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Blakeslee, Harold Law, active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Blankingship, Alexander Hugo, active 1924 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Blood, Charles Frederick, graduate member 1902 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Boggs, Theodore Harding, graduate member 1907 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Bolter, Ward H., active 1928 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Booth, Benjamin Noble, active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Borden, William R., active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Bousman, Henry Hugh, active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Bowen, Raymond Brower, active 1909 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Bower (Bauer), Ernest Turrell, active 1900 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Bozyan, H. Frank, active 1918 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Bradley, Harold Cornelius, honorary member 1905 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Bradley, John Smith Jr., active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Bradley, Wilmot Hyde, active 1918 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Brandt, Marvin Rudolph, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Brennan, Edward James, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Brockett, Earle Camp, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Brooke, Walter Edwin, active 1910 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Brooks, Wendell Stanton, active 1907 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Brown, Albert Raffles, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Brown, Ernest Thorwell, active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Giles Gorton, honorary member 1915 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Brown, James William, active 1925 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Brown, Robert Elliot, active 1902 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Bruce, Edwin Ney, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Brundage, Frederick Herbert, active 1905 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Bryant, Carl Herbert, active 1902 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Bull, Amasa Cobb, active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Bull, Irving Crawford, charter member n.d. (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Bull, Irving Horton, active 1925 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Bunker, Raymond Uhler, active 1902 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Burr, Julian Penfield, active 1907 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Burrell, Harold Paul Charles, active 1932 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Burtner, Elmer Edwin, active 1908 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Burton, John McNab, active 1915 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Burton, Marion LeRoy, active 1904 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Bush, William Mason, active 1933 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Bushnell, Paul Palmer, active 1919 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Calhoun, Robert Lowry, active 1915 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Callahan, Richard Michael, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Camp, Charles Clark, honorary member 1901 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Campbell, David Argyle, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Campbell, Kleber Alexander, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Carlson, Frank Alfred, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Carlson, Robert Irving, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Carrier, Augustus Stiles, honorary member n.d. (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Carver, George, active 1925 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Case, Raymond Bailey, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Case, Samuel Winship, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Chadburn, Alfred Jr., active 1927 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Chalker, Walter Chapin, active 1904 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Chambers, Wallace Bruce, active 1913 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Chaney, Clarence Edward, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Chapman, William Harmon, active 1910 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Cheney, Harold William, active 1916 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Chidsey, Samuel Ford, active 1920 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Clark, Arthur Bryan, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Clark, Eliot Round, active 1900 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Clark, Ralph E. Jr., active 1934 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Clark, Webster Kimball, active 1902 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Clearwater, Thomas Hoffman, active 1924 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Clements, Donald Simonds, active 1918 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Clingan, Bruce Waid, active 1918 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Condit, Paul Brainard, active 1901 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Connonly, Lawrence Michael, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Conrad, Ralph Victor, active 1922 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Cooke, Albert Mosher, active 1919 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Cooke, Warren, active 1928 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Corcoran, Thomas Francis, active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Corcoran, William Mansfield, active 1918 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Cornell, Edward Fahmstock, active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Cornwell, Martin Taylor, active 1913 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Cowan, Thomas Beveridge, active 1925 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Cowling, Donald John, active 1905 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Cross, Samuel Avery, active 1916 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Curtis, Harry Alfred, honorary member n.d. (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Daly, James Joseph, active 1934 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Davis, Boothe Colwell, active 1921 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Davis, Francis Breese, active 1905 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Davis, Noah Swan Jr., active 1924 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Davis, Stanton Hoffman, active 1916 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Davison, Herbert Milton Jr., active 1926 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Dawson, James Arthur, active 1915 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Decherd, Kirtland Wilcox, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Decker, William Thomas, active 1923 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Degnan, William Martin, active 1933 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Deming, Clinton Demas, active 1903 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Deming, Edward Adams, active 1902 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Dewitt, John Warren, active 1923 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Deyo, John Maurice, active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Diehl, Frederick Brereton, active 1915 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Dixon, Vincent Claude, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Dobson, Percy Grenside, active 1920 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Dodd, Frederick Ferriss, active 1903 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Dole, George Stuart, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Dole, Louis Alexander, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Doolittle, Frank Baldwin, active 1911 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Downs, Frederick Robert, active 1917 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Doyle, Maurice Aloysius, active 1922 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Dreisbach, Alfred Gerry, active 1914 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Drysdale, Alexander, active 1919 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Dwyer, Maurice John Jr., active 1932 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Easton, James Gordon, active 1925 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Edwards, Herbert Nicholas, active 1906 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Eggleston, Richard Cunningham, active 1908 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Eichmann, Arthur William, active 1933 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Ellis, Henry Gibbs, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Ellis, Matt Locke, active 1924 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Elmore, George Orton, graduate member 1904 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Ely, Arthur Edgar, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Farnham, Myrlon Atkin, active 1917 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Fennel, Justus John, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Fennell, William George, active 1928 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Ferguson, Franklin Alexander, active 1910 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Ferguson, James Stancliffe, active 1925 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Ferguson, Robert, active 1900 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Ferguson, Roy Cameron, active 1915 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Fernald, Henry Barker, active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Field, Francis Lightbody, active 1914 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Finney, William Edward, active 1920 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Fisher, Agnew, active 1928 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Flather, Clifton Curtis, active 1925 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Flint, Theodore Carpenter, active 1923 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Foerster, Max Henry, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Foord, William Malcolm, active 1907 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Forbes, Allen Harris, active 1915 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Foster, Graham, active 1908 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Foster, John Stuart, active 1916 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Foster, Stuart Olive, active 1922 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Fox, Denman Fleming, active 1903 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Fox, George Graham, active 1928 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Fox, Thomas, active 1908 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Fraser, Lewis Hasselman Davis, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Frederick, Wilson David, graduate member 1908 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Frizzell, Richard Hanna, graduate member 1932 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Gambrill, Howard Jr., active 1928 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Gatchel, Theodore Dodge, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Gaylord, Charles William, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Gaylord, Donald David, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Gibson, Julian Burr, active 1914 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Gibson, Newell Clarence, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Gillon, Frank Patrick Jr., active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Godfrey, Conrad Albert, active 1930 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Gold, Theodore Sedgewick, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Goodwin, Albert Hooker, active 1927 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Gordman, Howard Strauss, active 1932 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Gourlie, Howard Wallace, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Graham, James Richard, active 1930 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Grinnell, Edward Murray, active 1910 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Groce, William Marvin, active 1923 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Gulliver, Carl Chester, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Gulliver, Robert Huntington, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Haight, Jesse Johnston, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Hail, William James, active 1903 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Hains, George Jr., active 1907 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Hall, Lamont Andrew, active 1906 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Hamilton, George Hall, active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Hammer, Charles Keller, active 1927 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Hammond, Edward, active 1933 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Hardy, Paul Osgood, active 1912 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Harkness, Robert Rae, active 1913 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Harlow, Ralph Volney, active 1907 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Harr, Richard Whitmore, active 1922 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Harrell, David Jr., active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Hart, Reeves Welch, active 1914 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Harwood, Douglas Amend, active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Hasbrouck, Augustus, active 1924 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Haven, George Augustus, active 1904 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Hawley, John Terrill, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 216)